unisportstream.com 2017-09-02

# Privacy Policy | uss

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your or other details to help you with your experience.  
When do we collect information?  
We collect information from you when you respond to a survey or enter information on our site.

How do we use your information?  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

How do we protect visitor information?  
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
We do not use Malware Scanning.  
We do not use an SSL certificate  
• We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers.

Do we use ‘cookies’?  
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.  
However, you can still place orders .

Third Party Disclosure  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

Third party links  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Fair Information Practices  
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
• Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
